[{"question":"which object is smaller?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The marble cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The dirt cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"How many cubes there?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"4"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has lower density?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large leather cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large dirt cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Is the large dirt cube heavier than the large leather cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object has larger friction?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large dirt cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large leather cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object has lower restitution?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium porcelain cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large dirt cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which quadrant will the large dirt cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which quadrant will the medium porcelain cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object will stop moving earlier?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large dirt cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium marble cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object will stop moving first?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large leather cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large dirt cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium marble cube travel to quadrant \u2162?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will there a collision in the quadrant \u2160?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"How many collisions will happen between objects?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"<=3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":">3"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the large dirt cube collide more than once?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the large dirt cube collide with the wall in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the large leather cube collide with the medium marble cube in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which objects is the first collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The wall and the large dirt cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large leather cube and the large dirt cube"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The wall and the large leather cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The large dirt cube and the medium marble cube"}],"answer":2},{"question":"Which objects is the last collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The wall and the medium porcelain cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium marble cube and the wall"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The large dirt cube and the medium marble cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The large leather cube and the medium porcelain cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the large leather cube collide with other objects after it stops moving?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1}]